pricelesspartner.com 2008-06-16

# Privacy Policy

Use of the Website and/or the Service is also governed by our Privacy Policy. The personal information (including sensitive personal information) you provide to us will be stored on our computers.

You consent to us using this information to build up a profile of interests, preferences and browsing patterns and to allow you to participate in the Services.

By using the services of this Website you acknowledge that:

(a) Pricelesspartner.com cannot ensure the security and privacy of information you provide through the Internet and your email messages, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the use of such information by other parties;

(b) Pricelesspartner.com is not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information which you provide to them and you should use caution in selecting the personal information you provide to others through the Service; and

(c) Pricelesspartner.com cannot assume any responsibility for the content of messages sent by other users of the Service, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the contents of any communications you may receive from other users. We cannot guarantee, and assume no responsibility for verifying, the accuracy of the information provided by other users of the Service.

We do not share any personal information with third parties, and we do not send advertising to our members.

**Monitoring of Information**

We reserve the right to monitor all advertisements, public postings and messages to ensure that they conform to the content guidelines which may be applicable from time to time.
